<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gtk Theming Guide</title>
    <link>https://surajmandalcell.github.io/Gtk-Theming-Guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gtk Theming Guide</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://surajmandalcell.github.io/Gtk-Theming-Guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>https://surajmandalcell.github.io/Gtk-Theming-Guide/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surajmandalcell.github.io/Gtk-Theming-Guide/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Basic Concepts The GIMP ToolKit (GTK) is a widget-toolkit used to create GUIs on a variety of systems (thus making GTK cross-platform). GTK (http://www.gtk.org/) is commonly and incorrectly thought to stand for &amp;ldquo;GNOME ToolKit&amp;rdquo;, but is actually stands for &amp;ldquo;GIMP ToolKit&amp;rdquo; because it was first created to design an user interface for GIMP. GTK is an object-oriented toolkit written in C (GTK itself is not a language). GTK is entirely open-source under the LGPL license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating GTK3 Themes</title>
      <link>https://surajmandalcell.github.io/Gtk-Theming-Guide/creating-gtk3-themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surajmandalcell.github.io/Gtk-Theming-Guide/creating-gtk3-themes/</guid>
      <description>Creating GTK3 Themes To create a GTK3 theme, developers can start with an empty file or they can use a pre-existing theme as a template. It may help beginners to start with a pre-existing theme. For instance, a theme can be copied to the user&amp;rsquo;s home folder and then the developer can start editing the files.
The general format for a GTK3 theme is to create a folder named after the theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Icon Theme</title>
      <link>https://surajmandalcell.github.io/Gtk-Theming-Guide/creating-icon-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surajmandalcell.github.io/Gtk-Theming-Guide/creating-icon-theme/</guid>
      <description>Creating Icon Theme Not only can Linux users customize the desktop theme, but they can also change the icons. Icon-theme packs are easy to make, install, and obtain. Many Linux users may find it helpful to learn how to change icons, edit them, get more, etc.
Icon Location Icons may be stored in &amp;ldquo;~/.icons&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;/usr/share/icons&amp;rdquo;. Icons that are in &amp;ldquo;~/.icons&amp;rdquo; are only accessible to the owner of that home folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://surajmandalcell.github.io/Gtk-Theming-Guide/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:10:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surajmandalcell.github.io/Gtk-Theming-Guide/license/</guid>
      <description>The theme used to make this documentation hugo-material-docks by Martin Donah
Copyright (c) 2016 Digitalcraftsman &amp;lt;digitalcraftsman@protonmail.com&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt; Copyright (c) 2016 Martin Donath &amp;lt;martin.donath@squidfunk.com&amp;gt; Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;quot;Software&amp;quot;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions: The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gtk Theming Documentation</title>
      <link>https://surajmandalcell.github.io/Gtk-Theming-Guide/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:07:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surajmandalcell.github.io/Gtk-Theming-Guide/main/</guid>
      <description>Overview If you are a linux user and unsatisfied with the current theme collection want to create new theme or modify current one then this documentation is for you Many Linux desktops supporting themes. A theme is a particular appearance or &amp;ldquo;****&amp;rdquo; for the GUI. Users can change the theme to make the desktop look different. Usually, users also change the icons. However, the theme and icon-pack are two separate entities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>